https://www.thestudiodirector.com/privacy-policy

Order Now
Privacy PolicyThe Studio Director and OnVision Solutions, Inc. Our Use of Your Personal Information.
OnVision will ask you to provide information that personally identifies you, your location or your contact information when you purchase our software, request information from us, or register on our site for any other reason. We will use your personal information to fulfill your specific request and also to make contact with you related to that request. For example, when you provide personal information to purchase a license for The Studio Director software, we will use that information to configure the software for your use, but we will also use that information to contact you about billing and service matters or if we have a question or dispute about our license with you. If you contact us with questions about our software products, we will use your contact information to answer your specific questions, but may also use your personal contact information to provide additional materials about our software products at a later date.
If you purchase our Studio Director software, OnVision will consider information about your business that is used and stored in our software to be personal information. This includes information about your class schedules, your students and their families, and financial information.
OnVision will access your personal information and/or share it with third parties only for the following purposes: (i) as needed to confirm compliance with the terms of your license agreement or to enforce our rights under a license agreement; (ii) to provide upgrades, support or maintenance; (iii) if required to do so by law or to comply with legal process; (iv) to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of the public; or (v) in connection with a merger, consolidation or sale of substantially all assets of OnVision. OnVision will not sell your personal information to anyone, except that OnVision may sell all rights to some or all of our products and the sale of your personal information will be part of that sale.
OnVision is committed to ensuring the security of your personal information. OnVision stores your personal information in secure operating environments that are not accessible by the general public. Credit card numbers are used only for processing payment. Credit card information is accepted only through a portion of our website that encrypts the credit card information before transmission for your added protection.
Our Use of Non-Personal Information
OnVision also gathers and uses data that includes some of your personal information, but in a way that removes all of the parts of the personal information that could be used to identify you. That information is used for analyzing the effectiveness of various marketing strategies and also for analyzing the performance and use of our products. We may share this collected information for marketing or product improvements.Cookies
Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to your computer. Our products and websites use only “per session” cookies. These cookies do not collect information from your computer, they do not personally identify you, and they are completely erased when you close your web browser. They are used to maintain session identification while you are logged into the website. Most browsers allow users to refuse cookies. Please refer to the information about your browser. You must accept “per session” cookies to use our software.
Unsolicited Commercial Emails
OnVision is committed to complying with the requirements of the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003. OnVision is taking care and has implemented commercially reasonable practices and procedures designed to effectively prevent sending a commercial electronic mail messages to anyone who has let us know that they do not want to receive those messages.
Opting Out and Complaints
In order to opt out of receiving commercial email messages from The Studio Director or OnVision Solutions please send an e-mail to support@thestudiodirector.com. If, after 10 business days, you are still receiving commercial email messages from The Studio Director or OnVision Solutions, please let us know immediately by calling this toll-free number 877-688-3870. You may also use these contacts if you have any other questions or complaints about the operation of our website.
The Studio Director
PO Box 3221, Monument, CO 80132
OnVision Solutions, Inc.
The Studio Director is owned and operated by OnVision Solutions, Inc. OnVision Solutions is a provider of custom Internet applications and software consulting for all types and sizes of businesses. Utilizing state-of-the-art technologies and methods, OnVision Solutions delivers results that will increase your profitability
Technology can revolutionize business processes; it can provide intuitive and accurate information for decision makers to make better and quicker business decisions; it can enable efficiencies in the day-to-day processes and increase a company’s profitability.
OnVision Solutions, Inc.
Increasing Your Business Profitability Through Custom Software Solutions
The HUB3601 Walnut St Suite 410Denver, CO 80205Phone: 1-877-688-3870Email: info@thestudiodirector.com
© The Studio Director. 2019
